Sangoro!
سانغورو
Leave Otoko with me!
دع أوتوكو لي
Thanks, Usohachi!
شكرًا يا أوسوهاتشي
I'll leave the dinosaur to you!
سأترك الدّيناصور لك
Sure, I've got him!
نعم، سأتولّى أمره
Two-Sword Style:
أسلوب السّيفين
Otoro!
ردّ تسلّق البرج
Diable Jambe:
ساق الشّيطان
Concassé!
سحق
Zorojuro's so strong!
زوروجورو قويّ جدًّا
He's keeping pace with Boss Kyoshiro!
إنّه ندّ مناسب للزّعيم كيوشيرو
Don't do this, ronin.
من الأفضل أن تتوقّف أيّها الرّونين
Who is this guy?!
من يكون؟
It seems luck is on my side.
يبدو أنّ الحظّ يقف إلى جانبي
The Orochi Oniwabanshu The Wano Shogun's Personal Ninja Force
قوّات النّينجا الخاصّة بشوغن وانو “أونيابانشو أوروتشي”
The Orochi Oniwabanshu is here!
أونيابانشو أوروتشي هنا
As Hawkins said,
كان هوكينز محقًّا، يبدو أنّ كل أفراد قراصنة قبّعة القشّ هنا في بلاد وانو
It doesn't matter who; just capture one.
كلّ ما نحتاجه هو واحد منكم، لا أهتمّ من يكون
A round of torture after we capture you will reveal your true objective.
سنكتشف هدفكم هنا من خلال الإمساك بكم ثمّ تعذيبكم
Attack!
لننطلق
– Yes, sir!
حاضر
Sorcery, huh?
شعوذة؟
Ninpo:
نينبو
Infernal Biwa!
عود الجحيم
That's just a damn gun!
إنّه مجرّد مسدّس لعين
Toko!
توكو
Rest assured!
لا تقلقي
You must flee the capital as quickly as possible!
اهربي من العاصمة في الحال
Leave this to me,
سأهتمّ بهم
the Soul King!
ملك السول
Soul!
الروح
A curse on you!
اللعنةُ عليكم
There it is again!
ظهر ثانية
The gashadokuro!
غاشادوكورو
That woman...
...تلك المرأة
She was with Zorojuro.
كانت مع زوروجورو
Fujin. Raijin.
فوجين، رايجين
– Yes, sir!
حاضر
Follow that woman.
طاردا تلك المرأة
I thought you'd show up...
عرفت أنّك قادم
Trafalgar Law.
ترافالغار لاو
– Captain!
أيها القبطان
We're sorry, Captain!
نعتذر أيها القبطان
Getting caught caused you trouble!
أسرُنَا وضعَكَ في وضعٍ حرج
There should be one more. A polar bear.
ما الّذي فعلتموه بدبّنا الأبيض؟
With your ability, you'd have them out of there in an instant.
بإمكانك إخراجهم من هناك في رمشة عين بقدرتك
Only an idiot would put all the hostages where you can see them.
أيُّ الحمقى قد يُبقي كلّ رهائنه في مكان واحد واضح؟
You'll join them in that cage.
سأزجّ بك في ذلك السّجن أيضًا
Don't push your luck.
لا تستفزني
Haven't you learned anything?
ألم تتعلّم أيّ شيء؟
Have you?
أخبرني
You cannot defeat me.
لا يمكنك الإطاحة بي
It hurts!
هذا مؤلم
Shachi!
شاتشي
I have four lives right now.
لديّ أربع حيوات الآن
You can kill me only after your three crew members...
...بإمكانك تقطيعي فقط بعد أن تقتل
are dead.
الأعضاء الثّلاثة من طاقمك
That's right. That'll do just fine.
نعم، تصرف بأدب
Diable Jambe:
ساق الشّيطان
Concassé!
سحق
Just what I'd expect from the Vinsmoke bloodline.
واضح تمامًا أنّ دماء فينسموك تجري في عروقك
I told you to never speak that name again!
نهيتُكَ عن ذكر ذلك الاسم ثانيةً
You're also the man behind Soba Mask, aren't you?
كما أنّك تنكّرت أيضًا كمقنّع السّوبا، صحيح؟
No clue.
ومن يدري؟
Apparently, I'm damn attractive to dinosaurs.
أعتقد أنّني محبوب لدى الدّيناصورات فقط
You really want me to cook you that badly?
تريدني أن أصنع منك وجبة بهذه الشّدّة؟
You'll find I'm nothing like that weakling Page One!
أنصحك ألّا تعتقد أنّني ضعيف كذلك الصعلوك
Even nasty ingredients are fun to cook with.
المكوّنات العنيدة تجعل الطّبخ أكثر متعة دائمًا
That voice!
...ذلك الصّوت
The voice of beauty!
لجميلة ما
The beauty's under attack.
إنّها تتعرّض للهجوم
Diable Jambe...
ساق الشّيطان
Extra Haché!
لحم مفروم فاخر
She's waiting for help.
إنّها بحاجة للمساعدة
I'm coming to you!
سأوافيك في الحال... لأكون بجانبك
Zorojuro!
زوروجورو-سان
You saved her.
أنت تحميها
So you are allies!
إنّها رفيقتك إذًا
Why the hell are they after you?!
لماذا يطاردونك؟
I'm sorry. I thought I hid my face.
...أعتذر، حاولت إخفاء وجهي، لكن
Moss Head knows that beauty?!
يعرف الطحلبي تلك الحسناء؟
That bastard!
ذلك الوغد
He has a lower bounty than me!
مكافأته أقلّ... من مكافأتي
Outskirts of Bakura Town Kuri
كوري خارج بلدة باكورا
Kin'emon!
كينيمون
Deceive me and my men with your trickery, will you?!
أكنت تحاول محاصرتنا؟
Wait, Ashura! Indeed, we've wronged you!
توقّف يا أشورا، نلتمس منك العذر
It was an attempt to stoke the fire within you!
...فعلتُ ذلك بغرض تحفيزك
That one thought was driving my actions.
ساقتني تلك الفكرة
Nevertheless, forgive me, Ashura!
...ولكن
I should have asked you like this in the first place.
وجب عليّ القدوم إليك بدل ذلك
To serve our lord and his cause,
كنت أبرّر أفعالي باسم سيّدنا
and being pressed for time, I took a hard line...
...ولم يكن لديّ ما يكفي من الوقت، لذلك لم يسعني إلاّ اللّجوء لإجراءات قصوى
But I could not have been more wrong!
لكنّني كنت مخطئًا بالكامل
Twenty years is a long time!
عشرون سنة مدّة طويلة
The world changes, as do people's hearts!
العالم بحدّ ذاته تغيّر فناهيك عن قلوب النّاس
I utterly failed to consider this...
لم أفكّر في ذلك قطّ
Rather, I averted my eyes from it!
كلاّ، حاولت ألاّ أرى ذلك
However, there are those in this country
لكنّني أدركت أنّه ما زالت هنالك بعض القلوب ذات الإيمان الثّابت الّتي لم تتغيّر في هذه البلاد
I saw this in Lord Yasuie...!
...عندما رأيت ياسويي-ساما
Our plan yet lives!
ما زالت خطّتنا آمنة
Lord Yasuie gave his life to deceive our enemy!
ضلّل ياسويي-ساما العدوّ من أجلنا مضحّيًا بحياته
The symbols tattooed on the ankles of those Orochi captured...
...العلامة على كواحل أولئك الّذين اعتقلهم أوروتشي
Those samurai know better than anyone that the moon tattoo is more than just a trend.
يعرف أولئك السّاموراي حقّ المعرفة أنّ وشم الهلال ليس مجرّد تصميم شائع
On the night of the Fire Festival, we will lay siege to Onigashima!
سنغير على أونيغاشيما في ليلة مهرجان النّار
After what happened, those samurai in the capital will be freed...
سيُطلق سراح أولئك السّاموراي في العاصمة بسبب ما حدث
and they will surely join us!
وأنا واثق أنّهم سينضمّون إلينا
We desperately need your help if we are to defeat Kaido and topple Orochi!
نحن بحاجتك بكلّ تأكيد للإطاحة بكايدو وأوروتشي
I beseech you! Fight alongside us, Ashura!
هلاّ قاتلت جنبًا إلى جنب معنا يا أشورا؟
Come with me.
...اتبعوني
I have something to show you.
ثمّة أمر أريد أن أريكم إيّاه
Prisoner Mining Camp Udon
منجم السجناء أودون
Oshiruko.
...أوشيروكو
Oshiruko!
أوشيروكو
She did it!
لقد نجحت
Olin, you're amazing!
أولين-تشان، أنت قويّة جدًّا
I'm done for...
...كلاّ، لقد فعلتها
What's that?
ما الّذي يحدث؟
We're under attack! The front gate has been destroyed!
!نحن نتعرّض للهجوم! دُمّرت البوّابة الأماميّة
Nonsense!
مستحيل
Who the hell is crazy enough to pull a stunt like that?!
من فعل أمرًا كهذا؟
You bastard! You won't get away with this!
دخيلة لعينة، سألقّنك درسًا
Prepare to die!
جهّزي نفسك
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث؟
The intruder has broken through the second gate!
اخترقت الدّخيلة البوّابة الثّانية
Now approaching the third gate!
إنّها تقترب من البّوابة الثّالثة الآن
What's happening?!
ماذا؟
The third gate is...
...البوّابة الثّالثة
– What the...?!
ما الّذي...؟
That's...
...هذا
Bi...!
...بيـ
Big Mom?!
بيغ مام؟
What?! Is this some kind of nightmare?!
ماذا؟ هل أنا أحلم؟
Big Mom...
...بيغ مـ... مام
It's Big Mom!
!إنها بيغ مام
What's that? Is it yummy?
ماذا؟ أهو لذيذ؟
Why is Big Mom here?!
لماذا هي هنا؟
I heard her ship sank!
سمعتُ أنّ سفينتها قد غرقت
I'm so hungry!
أنا جائعة
Sh-She...
...لا-لا أصدّق
broke through the steel gate!
أنّها دمّرت البوّابة الفولاذيّة
That old bag is dangerous as hell!
تلك العجوز خطيرة جدًّا
Big Mom's one of the Emperors, a rival of Kaido.
...إنّ بيغ مام إمبراطورة بحر مثل كايدو-سان
Why is she here in Udon?!
ما الّذي أتى بها إلى أودون؟
Oshiruko.
...أوشيروكو
Oshiruko!
أوشيروكو
Huh? Oshiruko?
ماذا؟ أوشيروكو؟
Otama, hurry over here!
أوتاما-تشان، تعالي بسرعة
I smell oshiruko!
أشمّ رائحة الأوشيروكو
Olin is calling for me!
أولين-تشان تناديني
Let's eat together!
لنأكله معًا
Wh-Why do they have oshiruko?!
لماذا يوجد أوشيروكو هنا؟
I risked my life for the lie of a lifetime!
قلتُ تلك الكذبة المميتة مخاطرًا بحياتي
And now the gate has been opened.
كما أنّ البوّابة قد فُتحت
I was concerned with how we would get in...
ظننت أنّ الدّخول سيكون مشكلة
Now we can rescue Big Bro!
لنذهب لإنقاذ أخي الكبير الآن
Momo, it's time to go!
مومو-كُن، لنذهب
Y-Yeah. Let's go save Luffy...
...نـ-نعم، لننقذ لوفي
You will not.
كلاّ
Otama and Lord Momonosuke, you must hide and wait out here.
عليكما الاختباء والانتظار في الخارج يا أوتاما-تشان ومومونوسكي-ساما
What?! Why?!
ماذا؟ لماذا؟
It's a given. The road ahead is too dangerous for you, Otama.
واضح تمامًا أنّ الوضع خطير عليكما بعد هذه المرحلة يا أوتاما-تشان
And Lord Momonosuke cannot be seen at any cost.
كما أنّه لا يجب أن يراك أحد يا مومونوسكي-ساما مهما كلّف الأمر
Hmm... I don't have a choice...
...نعم... ما باليد حيلة
Okiku, wouldn't it be bad if they find out you're alive too?
أوكيكو، لا يجب أن يعرفوا أنّك على قيد الحياة أيضًا
Th-That is true!
معك حقّ
I appreciate the input.
شكرًا على النّصيحة
I will disguise myself with this!
سأخفي هويّتي بهذا
This is...
...هذا
perfect!
مثاليّ
Rest assured, they can no longer identify me!
لن يعرف أيّ أحد من أكون
What's with you samurai and your faith in those face scarves?!
لماذا تظنّون أيّها السّاموراي أنّ قطعة قماش تغطّي الوجه قد تكون مقنِعة؟
Chopperemon.
تشوبايمون-سان
The boss of Udon is
...إنّ أودون تحت سيادة
Queen, Superstar of the Beast Pirates.
أحد النجوم البارزين في قراصنة الوحوش، واسمه كوين
Keep that in mind as we proceed.
لنكن حذرين
Hey, you old bag! You said something about my oshiruko?!
أيّتها العجوز، أقلتِ أوشيروكو؟
That's right. Give me some right now!
نعم، أعطني إيّاه بسرعة
Oh, my. Just a little longer.
مهلًا، مهلًا، ستتناولينه قريبًا
I heard I could eat a lot of it here, so I came all this way.
سمعتُ أنّه يمكنني أكل كثيرًا منه هنا لذلك قطعت كلّ هذه المسافة
Stop screwing with me. Who the hell told you that?!
لا تعبثي معي، من أخبرك بهراء كهذا؟
You think you'll eat a lot of it?
يمكنك أكل كثير منه؟
Did you know this red bean soup is my favorite and decided to steal it?!
هل أتيت إلى هنا لسرقته على علم أنّه طعامي المفضّل؟
Hey, wait, you two! Pull them out of the water first!
مهلًا أيّها الأغبياء، اسحبوهما أوّلًا
While you're going at it, Jaggy and that other guy are gonna drown!
سيغرق المسنّن ورفيقه بينما تتحدّثون بأمور تافهة هكذا
What's the matter with you?!
هذه ليست أمورًا تافهة
Uh-oh! He's completely lost it!
سُحقًا، فقد صوابه بالكامل
He's started to transform!
بدأ يتحوّل
Oshiruko is like oxygen to me.
الأوشيروكو كالهواء الّذي أتنفّسه
It's my lifeblood!
إنّه يبقيني حيًّا
Are you really going to fight?!
هل ستقاتل؟
Please wait, Your Awesomeness!
انتظر رجاءً يا كوين-ساما
Cross Big Mom over food, and you'll be in big trouble!
إن قاتلت بيغ مام على الطّعام ستكون في ورطة كبيرة
It's too late. We can't stop him now!
فات الأوان، لا يمكننا إيقافه الآن
Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Brachiosaurus
فاكهة التّنّين، النّوع العتيق صنف البراكيوصور
I just heard a tremendous noise...
...سمعت ضجة عالية توًّا
This is so scary.
أنا خائف
Hey, we've got a huge problem on our hands here.
مهلًا، نحن في وضع سيّئ
There's no more oshiruko. What should we do?
نفد منّا الأوشيروكو.... ماذا علينا فعله؟
It's true that we've got a lot of oshiruko here.
صحيح، لدينا كثير من الأوشيروكو هنا
But it's all mine!
لكنّه لي أنا وحدي
Oshiruko...
...أوشيروكو
Olin is a nicer version of Big Mom,
أولين عبارة عن نسخة ألطف من بيغ مام
so she might be bullied or attacked by Queen.
ربّما تتعرّض للتّنمّر أو الأذيّة على يد كوين
I see... So you're the one with the oshiruko.
فهمت... الأوشيروكو في حوزتك
I don't want to hear you utter the word "oshiruko" in front of me again.
إيّاك أن تتلفظي بأوشيروكو أمامي ثانية
Get out of here, you old bag!
ارحلي أيّتها العجوز
What?!
ماذا؟
Just give me...
...أعطني
the oshiruko...
...الأوشيروكو
already!
في الحال
What?!
ماذا؟
Olin!
أولين-سان
– Your Awesomeness!
كوين-ساما